<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata>
    <name>Mega Satan in Greed Mode (+Delirium)</name>
    <directory>mega satan in greed mode</directory>
    <id>2928156221</id>
    <description>No more useless key pieces in Greed Mode! The Mega Satan door will now spawn after defeating Ultra Greed.

After defeating Mega Satan, a big chest, fresh donation machine, and golden penny will spawn. A door will also open allowing you to exit the room.

To get key pieces from Devil Rooms, you can use either of these mods:
[list]
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2732699827]Satan in Devil Rooms (+Fallen Angels)[/url]
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2897716537]Devil Keys[/url]
[/list]

Mod Config Menu will give you the option to fight Mega Satan instead of Ultra Greed or Mega Satan after Ultra Greed.

If you have Repentogon then you'll get Mega Satan completion marks, and built-in characters will earn their achievements. Modded characters may require some additional work.

Note: Don't skip Ultra Greed if you're trying to get your Greed Mode unlocks.

Update: Once you defeat Mega Satan or Ultra Greedier, stairs will spawn allowing you to fight Delirium. If you bring a Fool card, you can also fight Delirium after Ultra Greed. Sprite support for the following mods has been added (must be installed separately):
[list]
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2662678652]Unique Delirium Boss Door[/url]
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2810291641]Unique Delirium Door but Fancy[/url]
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=3280852083]Ultra Greed in Normal Mode[/url] (better ultra greed sprites for delirium)
    [*][url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1914928683]Ultra Greed Form for Delirium[/url] (don't install &quot;Greed Delirium&quot; if it prompts you)
[/list]

After defeating Delirium, a big chest, fresh donation machine, and cards(?!) will spawn. If you have Repentogon then you'll get Delirium completion marks, and built-in characters will earn their achievements.

Recommendation: If you're not using Repentogon then you should install [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2926219587]NoDelirium Fix[/url] so the Ultra Greed doors don't glitch out Delirium.</description>
    <version>1.33</version>
    <visibility>Public</visibility>
    <tag id="Lua"/>
    <tag id="Rooms"/>
    <tag id="Bosses"/>
    <tag id="Tweaks"/>
</metadata>
